嗨
Hey.
我刚拿到教师评监表 你们听这个学生写的
I just got my teacher evaluations. Check out what this one student wrote.
"我爱盖勒博士的课 令人大呼过瘾"
"I loved Dr. Geller's class. Mind-blowing lectures.
"盖勒博士 您是古生物学系的猛男"
Dr. Geller, you are definitely the hottie of the Paleontology Department."
"古生物学系的猛男们"
Ah, "Hotties of the Paleontology Department."
做成月历一定大卖
There's a big-selling calendar, huh?
那是谁写的？
Who wrote it?
我也想知道 但评监表是匿名的
I wish I knew, but the evaluations are all anonymous.
- 期末考考卷还在吗？ - 在啊
- Do you still have their final exams?     - Yeah.
你可以拿考卷来对笔迹 就知道仰慕者是谁了
Match the evaluation to the exam with the same handwriting and there's your admirer.
只要和女色有关 他就成了大天才
A hot girl's at stake and all of a sudden he's Rain Man.
等等 为何确定是个女生？
Hey, wait a minute, wait a minute. Why are we so sure that this is a girl?
是女生
It's a girl.
总之没差
Anyway, it wouldn't matter, okay?
- 因为我是老师 她是学生   - 校规说不行？
- Because I'm a teacher. She's a student.     - Oh, is that against the rules?
- 没有 但是会有争议   - 了解
- No, but it is frowned upon.     - I see.
而且年龄差那么多
Besides, there's a big age difference.
你就这么想 等你90岁...
Think of it like this. When you're 90...
我知道 我90她就80
I know, when I'm 90, she'll be 80...
感觉就差不多了
and it won't seem like such a big difference.
不是 我不是要说这个
No, that's not what I was gonna say at all.
我是说等你90岁
What I was gonna say is when you're 90...
还能拥有跟二十岁小妹妹恋爱的回忆
you'll still have the memory of what it was like to be with a 20-year-old.
老友记 第六季 第十八集
嘿 钱德 你知道你那个 当上电影导演的大学同学吗？
Chandler, you know that girl you went to college with who became a movie director?
知道 黛娜基史东 我们一起修动作课
Oh, yeah, Dana Keystone. She was in my movement class.
什么是动作课？
What's a movement class?
钱德在假装他没修默剧
It's Chandler's way of pretending he didn't take mime.
总之她要导艾尔帕西诺的新片
Listen, anyway, she's directing the new Al Pacino movie.
- 你得帮我争取试镜   - 我不知道 我们10年没联络了
- You gotta get me an audition.     - Oh. I haven't talked to her in like 10 years.
不 求求你 就当我欠你
Oh, no, no, no. Please, Chandler, I would owe you so much.
你本来就欠我 你欠我3千4百...
You do owe me so much. You owe me 3400...
老兄 你干嘛转移话题？
Hey, hey, dude. Why you changing the subject? What?
- 你打不打电话？ - 好吧 我试试看
- Will you make the call or what?     - Okay, I'll try.
万岁 谢了 你最好了
All right. Thanks, you're the best.
试镜是星期四截止 我星期四之前得过去
The last day of auditions is Thursday, so I gotta get in by Thursday.
记得星期四就对了 你记得吗？
Just remember Thursday. Thursday. Can you remember Thursday?
星期二吗？
Yeah, so Tuesday?
是星期四 你如果记不住
Thursday. Look, if you need help remembering, just think of it like this.
就记是第三天 星期一 一天
The third day. All right? Monday, one day.
星期二 二天
Tuesday, two day.
星期三 三天？哪一天？星期四
Wednesday, when, huh, what day? Thursday.
第三天 好吗？
The third day, okay?
- 谢谢你   - 不客气
- Thank you.     - Okay.
- 嘿 摩妮卡 我要听留官   - 你在厕所里想到这个？
- Hey, Mon, I'm gonna check my messages.     - You just thought of that in there?
当然 生理需求结束 她想知道还有谁需要她
Sure, you know, nature called. She wants to see who else did.
喂？
Hello?
呃...
Uh...
瑞秋
Rachel.
我们家有人 快报警
You guys, someone is in our apartment. Call the cops.
你在用电话
You're on the phone.
- 哦 天哪...   - 什么？
- Oh, my God.     - What?
天哪 谢谢你 是消防队
Oh, my God. Thank you. That was the Fire Department.
-  家里失火了   - 天哪 有多严重？
- There was a fire at our place.     - Oh, my God. How bad was it?
他没说 但失火总是不太妙
He didn't say, but it was a fire. I'm guessing not very good.
- 快走吧   - 快点
- Come on, we gotta go.     - Phoebe, come on.
笑什么笑？有什么好笑的？
What are you smiling about? What is so funny?
我要应徵的角色是消防队员 这真是天意
The part I wanna audition for is a fireman. This is so meant to be.
哇 你这学期的成绩给得很大方喔
Wow. Looks like you were very generous with your grades this semester.
- 盖勒教授？ - 是？
- Professor Geller?     - Yeah? Huh?
我只是要说我很喜欢你的课
I wanted to say how much I enjoyed your class.
谢谢你 非常成谢
Oh, thank you. Thanks very much. Ow.
很不好意思 在评监表说你是猛男
I'm a little embarrassed about calling you a hottie on my evaluation.
- 那是你？ - 对
- That was you?     - Yeah.
我后来觉得怪怪的 你是老师 我是学生
I felt a little weird about it. You're a teacher. I'm a student.
但或许你愿意和我约会？
But would you maybe wanna go out with me sometime?
喔 我... 这样恐怕不太好
Oh, I... Heh. I don't think that would be the best idea.
我想说学期结束后
Oh, because I was thinking, um, the semester's over.
- 你就不是我的老师了   - 什么时候？
- You're not my teacher anymore.     - What time?
当我没说 你已经给我A了
Oh, you know what? Forget it. I see you already gave me an A.
- 了解   - 开玩笑的
- Gotcha.     - I'm kidding. Ha-ha-ha.
- 哦 哈哈   - 哈哈
- Oh. Ha-ha-ha.     - Ha-ha-ha.
说真的 什么时候？
So seriously, what time?
借过 借过 你好
Coming through. Oh. Coming through. Oh. Hello. Hi.
不对 借过
No, right. Coming through.
- 噢   - 还好嘛
- Oh.     - Okay. Well, it's not so bad.
灾情主要集中在卧房
Most of the damage was contained to the bedrooms.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
老兄 这星期四可以跟你借制服吗？
Hey, buddy, you think I could borrow your uniform this Thursday?
- 什么？ - 乔伊 人家在忙
- Excuse me?     - Joey. He's working.
你穿一定很帅
You would look good in that.
- 灾情如何？ - 很惨 非常惨
- Uh-oh. How bad is it?     - Oh, it's bad, it's really bad.
只有一把斧头没被烧到 我根本不记得有买过
The only thing that isn't burned is an ax, which I do not remember buying.
- 瑞秋你的呢？ - 东西都烧光了
- How's your room, Rach?     - Everything's ruined.
床铺 衣服 你看我最喜欢的蓝毛衣
My bed, my clothes. Look at my favorite blue sweater.
那不是我的吗？
Isn't that mine?
好 我对你的损失深感遗憾
Fine. I'm sorry for your loss.
这里暂时不能住人
You're not gonna be able to live here for a while.
- 你们有地方去吗？ - 哦 哇
- You ladies have a place to stay?     - Oh. Wow.
好 你给我听着 老兄
Okay, look, pal...
我现在没心情被搭讪
I am not in the mood to be hit on right now.
不过要是你给我电话 我改天会打给你
But if you give me your number, I will call you some other time.
她们可以跟我们住
Yes, they can stay with us.
请问起火原因是什么？消防员
Have you figured out what started the fire, Mr. Fireman?
你们有人抽烟吗？
Well, uh, do either of you smoke?
没有
No, not usually.
- 不过现在来一根也好   - 不是
- But yeah, I could use one now. Thanks.     - No, no.
- 你们有人点蜡烛烧香吗？ - 有 我常点 我很喜欢
- Do you light candles, burn incense?     - Yes, I do all the time. I love them.
天哪 是我害的
Oh, my God, I did it. It's me, it's me.
我把房子给烧了
I burned down the house. I burned down the house!
菲比 别激动 没有必要怪谁 好吗？
Okay, Phoebe, calm down. There's no need to place blame. Okay?
我警告过她
I warned her about those candles.
能聊聊真好 居然这么久了
It's great to catch up. I can't believe how long it's been.
钱德 是不是...
Hey, Chandler, is that?
- 太好了 恭喜你   - 听着...
- Oh, that's great. Good for you.     - So, hey, hey, is it?
好 我们可以见个面...
Okay, so, yeah, maybe we can get together, um...
你等我一下...
Can you hold on for one second, please?
怎样？
What?
等你讲完 要不要叫彼萨？
When you're off the phone, you wanna get a pizza?
嗨 我回来了
Hi, I'm back.
听起来不错 好 就这么决定...好 再见
Yeah, that sounds great. Okay, well, we'll do it then. Okay, bye.
我什么时候试镜？我知道是星期四 但是几点？
Hey, listen, so when's my audition? I know it's Thursday, but what time?
嘿 我们没聊到那个
Hi. We didn't get to the audition.
- 我带她去喝咖啡时再说   - 啊
- I'm gonna take her to coffee and do it then.     - Ah.
哇 你要跟这个女生约会？
Wow, so now you're going on a date with this girl?
这不是约会 我们失联10年
Not a date. I haven't talked to her in 10 years.
总不能一通电话过去 就要人家帮忙
You can't call somebody you haven't talked to in 10 years and ask for a favor.
要讲人情世故 花点时间客套
There are rules, you know? You gotta put in some time.
没错 对不起
You're right, I'm sorry.
- 你又不是去见旧情人   - 我们只约过一次会
- It's not like you're going out with an ex.     - No, we only went out once.
你跟她交往过？
You dated her?
一次也没有
Not once.
干脆我也去找个前男友 来帮乔伊的忙
Great. Why don't I just go out with an ex, you know, and do Joey a favor?
想帮乔伊的忙 跟乔伊约会就好
Hey, you wanna do Joey a favor? Maybe you go out with Joey.
（中央咖徘厅）
真好 我朋友乔伊也在电影圈
Oh. That's great. My friend Joey's in the movie business.
你猜我那天遇见谁？豪伊
Mm. You know who I ran into from school? Howie.
- 我的朋友叫乔伊   - 嗯
- Hmm. My friend's name is Joey.     - Heh.
显然 豪伊在当剪接师
Apparently, Howie's editing now.
他打来问能不能剪我的新片
Yeah, he calls me up and asks me if he can edit my new movie.
你相信吗？
Heh. Can you believe that?
我们10年没联络
You know, I haven't spoken to him in, what, 10 years...
他居然来找我帮忙
and he asks me for a favor?
我一向很讨厌那家伙
Yeah, I've always hated that Howie.
连声好都没问
No "How you doing?" Heh.
连先喝杯咖啡都没有
Man, I mean, not even a cup of coffee first.
- 好大胆   - 就是啊
- Heh. The nerve, huh?     - Yeah.
续杯吗？
Refill?
事出突然 抱歉房里一团乱
Now, this is last-minute, so I want to apologize for the mess.
- 哦   - 谁在乎
- Oh.     - Who cares?
天哪
Oh, my God.
我住的时候绝对不是长这样
It sure didn't look this way when I lived here.
我知道
I know.
问题是
There's one problem, though.
这里只能睡一个人 另一个人得去住乔伊家
There's only room for one, so I guess one of you will have to stay at Joey's.
既然火算是我放的 你就睡这里吧
Well, since the fire was kind of my fault, I guess you should get to stay here.
嘿...
Hey, hey, hey, now.
谁也没有错 那是个意外
This was no one's fault, Pheebs, okay? It was an accident.
不 是我害的 你应该睡这里
It was my fault. You should get the nice room.
好吧
Okay. Whoo!
瑞秋 你是本饭店的首位贵客
So, Rach, you're the first guest at Hotel Monica.
摩妮卡饭店
Hotel Monica.
你得告诉我早餐想吃什么蛋
Just tell me how you like your eggs.
我打算瑞到床上给你
I thought I'd bring them to you, you know, in bed.
- 哦   - 你吃了这么多苦
- Aw.     - You've been through so much.
就是啊
I have.
这是我放彼萨的地方
This right here is where I keep the pizza.
纸巾在那里
And that's where the napkin is.
- 什么味道？ - 就是啊
- What's that smell?     - I know. I don't...
拜托 那么大一个班 你根本没有注意到我
Oh, please, it was such a big class. You never even noticed me.
当然有 你坐在爱困睡人森旁边
What? Of course I did. You sat next to Sleepy Sleeperson.
谁？
Who?
我记不住全班的名字
Oh. I had trouble remembering everyone's names...
就取绰号代替
so I came up with nicknames.
像你的另一边是发臭冯棕上衣
Like the guy on the other side of you was Smelly von Brown-Shirt.
没错
Oh, yeah. Ha, ha.
- 你有帮我取绰号吗？ - 没有
- So, um, did you have a nickname for me?     - Uh, no. No.
你有 是什么？
Yes, you did. What was it?
呃 是...
Um, it's...
可爱麦美眉
Cutie McPretty.
真好
Oh, that's so sweet.
说真的 今晚真的很开心
Listen, I gotta tell you, I'm having a great time.
你之前说师生约会很奇怪
You know how you said it might be weird, the whole student-teacher thing?
其实我也有同感 结果不会 一点也不会
And to be frank, I thought it would be too. But it's not. I mean, it's not at all.
- 盖勒博士   - 伯特
- Dr. Geller.     - Burt.
你昨晚睡得好吗？
So did you sleep well last night?
- 很好   - 是吗？
- I did.     - Yeah?
摩妮卡还在我的枕头上 放了一小片薄荷
I did. Monica was so sweet. She left a little mint on my pillow.
- 你猜乔伊在我枕头上放什么？ - 什么？
- Know what Joey left on my pillow?     - What?
口香糖
Gum.
找到起火原因了
Well, we determined the cause of the fire.
我知道 是我的蜡烛害的
Yeah, I know. It was my candle, my candle.
不是 浴室有个电器没拔掉
No, there was an appliance left on in the bathroom.
好像是卷发器
It looks like a curling iron.
- 我没用卷发器   - 总有人在用
- I don't use a curling iron.     - Well, someone does.
别看我 我的头发是直的 直的直的直的
Don't look at me, my hair's straight. Straight, straight, straight.
- 也可能是直发夹   - 哦
- It could've been a hair-straightener.     - Oh.
彼萨都放这里
This is where I keep the pizza.
纸巾呢？
And... Hey, where'd the napkin go?
好了 可不能让贵客眼睛疲劳
There you go. I wouldn't want my best guest to strain her eyes.
谢谢摩妮卡
Thanks, Monica.
- 你怕那个味道吗？ - 乔伊家的味道？
- Does that smell bother you?     - What, the smell from Joey's?
这里又闻不到
No, I can hardly smell it over here.
闻得到就说 我可以烤个派把它盖过去
Well, you let me know if you can. Because I can bake a pie to cover it.
- 有点闻得到 烤个派吧   - 好
- I can smell it a little. Bake the pie.     - Okay.
喂？
Hello?
在 请稍候 火场调查员找你
Oh, yes, one minute, please. It's for you. It's the fire inspector.
喂？我是菲比
Oh. Hello? Yeah, this is Phoebe.
是吗？
Really?
是的 所以直发夹不是
Yeah, so it turns out that it wasn't the hair-straightener...
起火原因
that started the fire.
不 是蜡烛
No, no. It was the candles.
把蜡烛点着不管实在不太好
Yeah. It's very not good leaving candles unattended.
消防学校最先教的事情之一...
In fact, one of the first things they teach you in fire school is...
呃...
Uh...
好 我该挂了
Uh, okay, well, I have to go now.
我们玩得好开心 她好棒
We had such a great time. She's incredible.
我以为年龄会造成问题 结果一点也不会
I thought the age difference might be a problem, but it wasn't.
伊丽莎白非常成熟
It wasn't at all. Elizabeth is very mature for her age.
有些人就是不懂
A concept lost on some people.
所以师生可以约会？
So it's okay to date a student?
也不是
Well, not really.
技术上没触犯校规
I mean, technically, it's not against the rules or anything.
但是会受争议
But it is frowned upon...
尤其是我们昨晚遇见的教授
especially by that professor we ran into last night.
属于自以为是的学者
Judgy von Holier-Than-Thou.
罗斯 小心一点
Just be careful, okay?
别被叫成麦泡学生教授
You don't wanna get a reputation as Professor McNails-His-Students. Ha, ha.
- 我该怎么办？ - 很简单
- Yeah. What should I do?     - Well, Ross, it seems pretty clear.
什么比较重要？别人的看法还是你的感觉？
I mean, what's more important, what people think or how you feel? Huh?
- 你得忠于你的心   - 乔伊 你说得真好
- Ross, you gotta follow your heart.     - Joey, that is so sweet.
- 嘿   - 嘿 你跟黛娜谈得怎样？
- Hey.     - Hey, hey. So how'd it go with Dana?
我星期四该不该空出时间来？
Any reason I should leave a block of time open, say, Thursday?
- 我说不出口   - 你说不出口？
- I couldn't do it.     - You couldn't do it?
别急 我需要更多时间 我们晚上要吃饭
Relax, I just need more time. We're going to dinner.
什么？你还要跟她出去
What? You're going out with her again?
- 跟谁出去？ - 大学的黛娜基史东
- Going out with who?     - Dana Keystone, from college.
喔 对 她不是...
Oh, yeah. Wasn't she, uh, mm?
不 那是黛娜卡普林
No, that was Dana Kaplan.
- 噢   - 啊
- Oh.     - Ah.
- 乔伊 你根本不认识她   - 随便啦
- Joey, you didn't even know her.     - Yeah, whatever.
故事真的好棒
Great story again.
好错综复杂
The yarns that you weave.
哈哈哈 哇哦
Ha-ha-ha. Woo-hoo!
我该走了
You know, uh, actually, I should get going.
留下来
Oh, no, no, no, stay, stay, because you should...
你应该留下来
You should stay.
哇哦
Wow.
我真的很受宠若惊
Oh, I am really flattered.
但是我对你没感觉
But I just... I don't feel that way about you.
- 不 我不是...不是   - 钱德 对不起
- Oh, no, no, no. That's not... No, no, no.     - I'm sorry, Chandler.
你人很好 我也不想伤害你
You know, you are such a sweet guy, and I don't wanna hurt you.
真希望有什么可以让你好过点
Oh, I wish there were something I could do to make you feel better.
不... 真的吗？
No, no, no... Really?
当然
Of course.
我真是太伤心了 我...
Well, it just hurts so bad, I, uh...
对不起
Oh, I'm sorry.
- 或许你可以做件事   - 什么事？你尽管说
- Well, maybe there is one thing you can do.     - What? Anything. Anything.
我是刚刚才想到的
Well, I mean, this is just off the top of my head now. Um...
我有个演员朋友
Ahem. But I have this friend, uh, this actor friend...
他要是知道一定会杀了我
and he would kill me if he knew that I was doing this, um...
但你可不可能让他去为你的电影试镜
but, um, would it be possible for him to get an audition for your movie...
就星期四吧？
say, on Thursday?
没问题
Absolutely.
但是我让你的朋友来试镜
But you'd really feel better about me rejecting you...
真的能让你好过一点？
if your friend can audition for my movie?
这是我的心愿 再见
Well, the heart wants what it wants. I'll see you later.
怎么样啊？
Hey. How's it going?
这5分钟都没什么变化
Well, not much has changed in the last five minutes.
其实有 我烤了饼干
Yes, it has. I made cookies.
不了 我还在消化你做的薯片
That's all right. I'm still full from your homemade potato chips, so...
但是饼干应该刚烤好就趁热吃
Oh. But you should eat them now because they're hot from the oven.
- 好   - 但不是在这里
- Okay.     - Oh. But not in here.
床上不能吃饼干 不能掉屑屑
Can't eat them in bed, remember? No crummies.
哦
Oh.
好 我马上出去
I'll be out in a second.
好
Okay.
- 你在干什么？ - 门锁不起来 对吧？
- What are you doing?     - This doesn't lock, does it?
- 乔伊 对不起   - 没关系 别在意
- Oh. Joey, sorry. Oh.     - Oh, it's all right, don't worry about it.
但是你看 会有污渍
No, but look. Oh, that's gonna leave a stain.
瑞秋 没关系 这是乔伊家
Rach, hey, it's fine. You're at Joey's.
- 真的吗？ - 当然 你看
- Really?     - Yeah, look.
- 嗯   - 是啊
- Huh.     - Yeah.
- 我没有这样吃过东西   - 我知道
- I've never lived like this before.     - I know.
哇 哈哈哈
Whoo! Ha-ha-ha.
别浪费了 这是食物
All right, well, don't waste it. I mean, it's still food.
接着要干嘛？要不要去喝酒？
What do you wanna do now, huh? You wanna go get a drink?
我不行
Uh, I can't.
- 你要念书？ - 不是 我要满21岁才行
- Oh, you have some studying to do?     - No, I have some turning 21 to do.
好的 哈哈
Okay. Ha, ha.
我以前念大学时 我们都...
You know, I remember when I was in college, we used to...
- 你干什么？ - 没事
- What are you doing?     - Nothing, I'm just...
我只是觉得好舒服
I'm so comfortable with you.
- 你怕被别人看见？ - 什么？
- Do you not wanna be seen with me?     - What?
当然不是 他们走了吗？
No, of course I do. Are they gone?
他们还在 不过我要走了
No, they're still here. But I think I'm about to leave.
什么？等下
What? No, no, wait, wait.
你说得对 这样太蠢了 管别人怎么想
You're right, this is stupid. Who cares what people think?
我们情投意合 对吧？这样并没有错
I mean, we like each other, right? There's nothing wrong with that.
来吧
Come on.
伯特、莉蒂亚、梅尔
Burt. Lydia. Mel.
- 这位是伊丽莎白   - 嗨
- This is Elizabeth.     - Hi.
你不是有修我的大众文化？
Aren't you in my Popular Culture class?
没错 莉蒂亚 伊丽莎白是学生
That's right, Lydia. Elizabeth here is a student.
我们在交往
And we're dating.
你们可以皱眉摇头
And you may frown upon that...
但我们不会再躲了
but we're not gonna hide it anymore.
你的饭碗砸定了
You are so fired.
- 什么？ - 你会被解聘
- What?     - They're gonna fire you.
跟学生交往是违规的
You can't date a student. It's against the rules.
真的？不只是受争议？
Really? It's not just frowned upon?
- 哦   - 啊
- Oh. Ah.     - Ah!
我最喜欢乔伊家了
I love it at Joey's.
去吧
There you go.
- 谢谢   - 漂亮
- Ooh. Thanks.     - Nice.
- 你星期四有事吗？ - 真好笑
- So you busy Thursday?     - Oh, very funny.
不晓得你记不记得 我的试镜就是星期四
I don't know if you remember, but my audition was supposed to be Thursday.
你帮我争取到了？
You got me the audition?
- 是啊   - 来抱抱
- Yeah.     - Oh, let's hug it up.
好...
Okay, okay, okay.
要是你入选还得了
What are you gonna do to me if you get the part?
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
- 我有事要找你   - 嗯哼
- Yeah, okay, I need to talk to you.     - Uh-huh.
我知道他们说直发夹是起火源
Now, I know that they said that the hair-straightener started the fire...
但我也有责任
but I think I'm partly at fault.
我没有告诉你 我放了新的卫生纸
You see, I didn't tell you, but, um, I had recently refilled the tissues.
那个太容易着火了
And so, you know, let's face it, that's just kindling.
所以我应该来住乔伊家
So I think it's better that I stay at Joey's.
不 菲比 都是我不好
No, no, no, Phoebe, this was my fault.
- 而且我在这里好得很   - 好吧
- Besides, you know what? I'm fine here.     - Okay.
- 钱德 摩妮卡在找你   - 是喔？
- Oh, Chandler, Monica's looking for you.     - Really?
- 好像跟饼干屑有关   - 不会吧 我那么小心
- Yeah, she said something about crummies.     - No, no, no. I was so careful.
好 你一定要跟我换 摩妮卡快把我逼疯了
Okay. You have to switch with me. Monica is driving me crazy.
没错 小姐们都想住乔伊家
That's right. All the ladies wanna stay at Joey's.
不要 我不想换
No, Phoebe, come on, I don't wanna switch.
拜托啦 我在这里可以扔纸巾
Please. Come on, I can throw wet paper towels here.
在对面你可以对着水槽吃饼干
No, but at Monica's, you can eat cookies over the sink.
我知道 对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
好吧 算了
All right, fine.
- 这个好像很好玩   - 哈哈
- This looks like so much fun.     - Ha, ha.
湿答答的
God, what a mess.
校规里真的有写
Wow, it actually is in the handbook.
我不能和你约会 或是在研究室放电磁炉
I can't date you or have a hot plate in my office.
我们居然不能再见面了
Oh, I can't believe we have to stop seeing each other.
不过谢谢你为我挺身而出
For what it's worth, I did appreciate you standing up for me.
我好感动
That felt really nice.
我更喜欢你了
Kind of made me like you even more.
我知道 我也很喜欢你 但是我们不能交往
I know, I know. I really like you too. But we can't date.
校规明文禁止师生恋
It's against the rules. It's forbidden.
哇哦
Wow.
- 怎么了？ - 光听你说校规"禁止"
- What?     - Just hearing you describe it...
就觉得好性感
as forbidden, it's really hot.
真的？
Really?
对
Yeah.
不管有多性感 这都是错的
Well, I don't care how hot it is, it's, uh... It's wrong.
- 别再说了   - 不 这是错的
- Stop it.     - No, no. It's wrong. It's...
这样很坏
It's naughty.
这是...
It's...
禁忌
taboo.
把书搁起来
Shut the book.
- 再去弄个电磁炉吧   - 哦
- Hey. Let's also get a hot plate.     - Oh.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey.
- 怎样啊？ - 怎样？
- So?     - So?
- 今天是星期四 试镜结果如何？ - 哈？
- It's Thursday. How was the audition?     - It's Thur...?
星期一一天 星期二二天 星期三三天？星期四...
Monday, one day. Tuesday, two day. Wednesday, when, huh, what day? Thur...
噢
Oh!